

Carlie Berry

Austin, TX | carlie.berry@yahoo.com | (361) 331-2395 www.linkedin.com/in/carlieb
Portfolio - https://carlieb889.github.io/CarlieBWorks/

Professional Summary

UX / UI Designer with medical coding and billing experience. I gained professional strength going up against big insurance companies fighting for patient's maximum rights and benefits. Recognized by the Donna Lowrey award for going above and beyond my job description, two years in a row from Ernest Health, Inc.

Top student of the 2019 UX/UI Bootcamp at the University of Texas. I now fight for user's rights by crafting data-driven digital products to build responsive web designs that increase businesses capacity for impact.

Skills

- Texas Notary exp 12-10-2022
- Agile Project Management
- Research & Analyzing Data
- Storyboarding
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- User Flows
- User Experience Design
- User Interface Design

- Invision, Figma, XD, Webflow
- Design Systems
- User Testing & Interviews
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Developer Handoff
- Presentations & Communication
- Time Management
- Problem Solving

Work History

UX Designer & Marketing Specialist | Freelance | Aug 2018 – Current

Uses market research and analysis to create user friendly marketing strategies for various Real Estate Agents. Driving increase of client traffic by creating online and print marketing, management and maintenance of agent's websites, online listings, and social media ads.

Senior Sales Admin | Kuper Sotheby's Intl Realty | Aug 2018 - Current

Assists in advancing a billion-dollar franchise by facilitating real estate listings from start to finish for clients (real estate agents): auditing contracts and legal documents, marketing, closings. Upload and maintain listings and marketing to multiple syndicating websites. Making sure all elements of a transaction and marketing of property meets TREC, ABOR, and Sotheby's brand and legal standards. User Experience Research for the client-side of our back-end management system. Training new hires and managing the Sales Admin Department for all Austin offices.

Event Coordinator | Side Hustle | Royal Fig Catering Company | March 2016 - Current

Coordinating and overseeing teams of staff to set up, serve, and break down high-end weddings.

Business Office Specialist | Children's Cardiology Associates | Dec 2015 – Aug 2018

Insurance Verification and Obtaining medical authorizations, Medical Billing and Coding

Admissions Specialist | Corpus Christi Rehabilitation Hospital | Oct 2013 – Dec 2015

Facilitating all patient referrals, hospitals admissions, insurance verification and authorizations, and patient discharge plans

Education

UX | UI Design Bootcamp, University of Texas